SEBASTIAN NICOLAS ARZANI DOMENGET

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE - DATA SCIENCE - PYTHON PROGRAMING



(+60) 017 386 7062



nclsarzani@gmail.com



Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia



For the past two years, I have been working on business intelligence and data science. In my previous job, I worked with social network inputs, doing data mining for user classification, strategic marketing and brand positioning. I have experience with analytical tools like Oracle Analytics Desktop, Power BI, Microsoft Azure and Microsoft Excel. Also with Google Cloud and its APIs (including Gmaps).

My main objectives are, to expand my knowledge in the business intelligence area, data business strategies and data science while working in consulting assignments delivering concrete business results.

EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2020

Data Scientist - Eye Watch Big Data Solutions

My responsibilities were divided into two main groups:

- Valuation of data architecture and quality.
- ETL. Tools evaluation and improvement.
- Clustering and machine Learning modeling

And:

- Client prospect
- Coaching
- Innovation

2016 - 2019

Stock Control - Peugeot Official after-sales Agency

Some of my responsibilities in this position were:

- IT Logistics Planning
- Reporting systems and Customer Account Monitoring and Control

2018- At the present

Data Scientist and Python developer - Freelance

As a freelancer I worked on Natural Language Processing projects, Web Scraping, Data Transformation and web services with Flask for data analysis.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- PYTHON
- ETL WEB SCRAPING SQL
- NATURAL LANGUAGE PROCESSING
- MODELING MACHINE LEARNING
- REPORTING

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- ACTIVE LISTENING
- WILLINGNESS TO LEARN
- Successful coaching
- Positive reinforcement
- Resilience
- TEAM WORKER

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH
- Spanish

COMPLEMENTARY KNOWLEDGE

- CODING OPTIMIZATION SEO
- LINK BUILDING STRATEGIES
- WEB SERVICES
- AVASCRIPT
- GEOREFERENCED DATA

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATES

Data Analytics for Business - 2020

Coursera, Online course authorized by University of Colorado Boulder

Introduction to data Analytics for business

Data Scientist - 2018 Digital House Coding School (Argentina)

Data Scientist with Python

Programing - 2016-2017

Coursera, Online course authorized by University of Michigan

- Getting Started with Python
- Python Data Structures
- Using Python to Access Web Data

COMMUNICATION AND ACHIEVEMENTS

When I started to work with Eye Watch there was no other Data Scientist in the team. It was my responsibility to take all necessary actions in order to maintain and improve the projects. I had to work with my copartners and help them to understand the potential of Data Science and how it could help us with day to day company's goals.

Further, I participated in strategic meetings, coaching of staff and as an intermediary on the interactions with others areas of the company. Finally after one year of work the mayor achievements were.

- Online reportings, and web based services.
- Georeferenced reportings for clientes and company as well as georeferenced attributes on company DB.
- Improvements and implementation of publics APIS for data extraction.
- Improvements with identification rate of bots on social networks inputs.

REFERENCES

Gustavo Cadeiras COO from Eye Watch: gdc@eyewatch.me Mariano Vidal Journalist Client: mvidal@gmail.com

Marcelo Blanco Supervisor Peugeot : mblanco@gmail.com